<MaterialEntry>
	<Key>RoomController_CD</Key>
	<Pages>
		<Page>
			<Paragraphs>
				<Title>
					<Text>Generic Room Controller</Text>
				</Title>
				<Icon>
					<Name>RoomController</Name>
					<Alignment>Center</Alignment>
				</Icon>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>This machine allows you to designate areas of your base for various behaviours. This has a number of advantages.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
        <Spacer/>
        <Paragraph>
          <Text>Generic Rooms offer a large performance boost, both when inside and outside of the room. Every room requires an Internal Airlock and an External Airlock. Placing a Room Controller will then prompt you through any issues found, and should be relatively straightforward.</Text>
        </Paragraph>
        <Spacer/>
        <Paragraph>
          <Text>Greenhouses will allow Hydroponic Bays to work much faster. They also put a very cool gaseous effect on the floor that can be used for effect.</Text>
        </Paragraph>
        <Spacer/>
        <Paragraph>
          <Text>Heated rooms confer 2 bonuses. Firstly, any cold effects on your suit are negated. Secondly, any machines suffering environmental Cold effects will work as normally, like Conveyors.</Text>
        </Paragraph>
        <Spacer/>
        <Paragraph>
          <Text>Filtered Rooms offer complete protection from any dangerous airborne particulates.</Text>
        </Paragraph>
        <Spacer/>
      
        
        
			</Paragraphs>
		</Page>
    <Page>
      <Title>
        <Text>Generic Room Controller</Text>
      </Title>
      <Icon>
        <Name>RoomController</Name>
        <Alignment>Center</Alignment>
      </Icon>
      <Paragraphs>
      <Paragraph>
        <Text>A number of machines require the specific control only rooms can offer.</Text>
      </Paragraph>

        <TwoColumnParagraph>
          <Left>
            Base Scanner
            Robot Arms
            Hydroponics
          </Left>
          <Right>
            Required
            4x speed boost
            Greenhouse
          </Right>
        </TwoColumnParagraph>
        <Spacer/>
        <Paragraph>
          <Text>Rooms can be made out of virtually any opaque material.</Text>
        </Paragraph>
        <Paragraph>
          <Text>To transfer items through the walls, use a Logistics Grommet. To transfer power through the walls, use a Power Grommet. Machines cannot be walls, with the exception of Minecart Track.</Text>
        </Paragraph>
        <Paragraph>
          <Text>Induction Plates are valid in both the Ceiling and Floor, to allow broad power transfer.</Text>
        </Paragraph>
        
      </Paragraphs>

    </Page>
				
	</Pages>
</MaterialEntry>

