<MaterialEntry>
	<Key>MagmaBorePlacement</Key>
	<Pages>
		<Page>
			<Paragraphs>
				<Title>
					<Text>MagmaBore Construction</Text>
				</Title>
				<Icon>
					<Name>MagmaBore Component</Name>
					<Alignment>Center</Alignment>
				</Icon>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>Cuts an enormous bore down to the magma caverns in order to flood the Cold Caverns with heat. Build in a 33wx3hx33d configuration (3276 total)</Text>
				</Paragraph>
	
				<Spacer/>
			
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>The MagmaBore will create us a shaft down to the Magma Caverns; once this is complete, we should be able to compress the magma and use it to finally wipe the CryoPlasm Spawner out - permenantly.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
				
				<Spacer/>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>The base of the MagmaBore is built in a 33 metre square shape, 3 metres tall. Once this is done, the base gantry will attempt to self-erect. This will require a clearance of 12 more metres; the area to be cleared will be marked off with a red box. Clear inside this area to progress to the main digistruct gantry.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
				
				<Spacer/>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>The main part of the MagmaBore will require a further 64 metres of clearance, for a total size of 33x80x33. Again, clear any detritus inside the blue box to proceeed to the final phase. We are going to need epic amounts of power to literally create this invincible drill from pure energy.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
				<Spacer/>
			</Paragraphs>
		</Page>
		
		<Page>
			
			<Paragraphs>
			<Title>
				<Text>MagmaBore Usage</Text>
				</Title>
				<Icon>
					<Name>MagmaBore Component</Name>
					<Alignment>Center</Alignment>
				</Icon>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>Once the drill has been fully digistructed, then boring can begin. We&#39;re estimating at least 100k power per second to run this slowly - perhaps much more! The more power available, the faster our progress will be. After we hit the Magma Caverns, we can start to pump the Magma up and use it!</Text>
				</Paragraph>
				<Spacer/>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>Magma should be pumped to a Magma Storage Unit via a standard Fluid Pipe. This can be located up to 256 metres from the MagmaBore. The Magma Storage can then be connected at a maximum distance of 512m to an active Cryo Inferno cannon. That in turn can permenantly end the CryoSpawner threat.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
				<Spacer/>
			</Paragraphs>
		</Page>
		
	</Pages>
</MaterialEntry>
