<MaterialEntry>
	<Key>ResearchStation</Key>
	<Pages>
		<Page>
			<Paragraphs>
				<Title>
					<Text>Research Station</Text>
				</Title>
				<Icon>
					<Name>Research Station</Name>
					<Alignment>Center</Alignment>
				</Icon>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>The research station provides the facilities needed to understand more about this planet; its minerals, fauna and flora. It allows you to process the information recorded by your scanning tool as well as research the new technologies to help you survive. Many of the more advanced research topics are beyond the capabilities of the research station and require assisance from a laboratory.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>To use the research station face is and press your interact key (default &#39;E&#39;). This will open the research terminal which contains three tabs for processing scans, recipes and projects.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
			</Paragraphs>
		</Page>
		<Page>
			<Paragraphs>				
				<Header>
					<Text>Processing Scans</Text>
				</Header>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>Your suit comes equipped with a scanning tool (default &#39;M&#39;), the secondary action on this tool allows you to scan an unknown material in the world. The tool will also automatically scan any unknown material absorbed by your build tool. This information is uplinked to the research station.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>The first tab in the research station lists any remaining unknown materials and allows you to process these scans to learn more about them. Processing the scan will cost power and grants the number of research points shown which can be used to research additional recipes or projects.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
			</Paragraphs>
		</Page>
		<Page>
			<Paragraphs>
				<Header>
					<Text>Researching Recipes</Text>
				</Header>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>Processing scans and completing research projects can unlock new recipies to be researched. These are typically new machines which can help you survive and progress on your journey. Each has a cost in research points and power, you should spend your research points carefully, if you run out you&#39;ll need to venture further afield in search new materials to scan.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
	
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>Most of the recipes you research can then be crafted in the manufacturing plant, some will require specialised construction facility. Check the survival handbook entry on the machine for more information.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>The research station can be powered directly from the Central Power Hub (CPH), however the power transfer rate will be limited when the CPH is low on power.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
			</Paragraphs>
		</Page>
		<Page>
			<Paragraphs>				
				<Header>
					<Text>Researching Projects</Text>
				</Header>
				<Paragraph>
					<Text>Projects typically improve your technology level in a particular area unlocking new recipes either directly or through the recipes tab in the research station. Simple projects can be performed by the research station alone at the cost of power and research points. More complicated projects require the assistance of the laboratory. The laboratory is itself a research project which must be unlocked.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
				<Paragraph>
					<ResearchRequirements>
						<Research>Advanced Research</Research>
					</ResearchRequirements>
					<Text>For more information on Laboratory research projects please visit the following guide.</Text>
				</Paragraph>
					
				<Link>
					<ResearchRequirements>
						<Research>Advanced Research</Research>
					</ResearchRequirements>
				
					<Target>
						<Chapter>laboratory research</Chapter>
						<Page>0</Page>
					</Target>
					<Text>Laboratory Research Guide</Text>
				</Link>
				<Link>
					<Target>
						<Chapter>unknown materials</Chapter>
						<Page>0</Page>
					</Target>
					<Text>Unknown Materials</Text>
				</Link>
			</Paragraphs>
		</Page>
		
	</Pages>
</MaterialEntry>

